TOHO CORPORATION
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE
WARRING STATE PERIOD...
Oichi Kittan, you better give up and
face the facts as an honorable ninja.
Kittan, do you plan to go to
the Takeda and disappear?
I don't know.
- What?
I don't know until I try...
I, Suzumeno Saburoza will
teach you, it's not that easy.
Oh, it's you who claims that
the best ninja of the Takeda...
Suzumeno, a human being
can't act only by plans.
It's heart. Follow your heart.
Takeda Shingen... bah!
I miss seeing him.
He's just like a cold and smelly fish.
One more animal, come out!
I give up!
I am Doko Harima and I'm
quite famous in Kanto.
Why are you giving up?
This isn't a suitable career for me.
I think, this job is not worth
putting my energy into.
Then, why did you follow me?
To kill you!
But I realized, I can't kill
an inexperienced man.
And...
And?
You might be stronger than I am...
I watched you, and you
didn't give him a chance.
You don't seem like a ninja.
You're right!
Being a ninja is not my style.
Oh! Here's some food.
Between Takeda's castle and Kiso valley...
you killed eighteen men,
including Suzumeno. Saburoza.
Well done.
You also did a good job counting...
If you're right, next will be number 19...
WARRING CLANS
(Sengoku Yaro)
Producer:
TANAKA Tomoyuki
Script:
SANO Ken OKAMOTO Kihachi
SEKIZAWA Shinichi
CAST
KAYAMA Yuzo HOSHI Yuriko
SATO Makoto
NAKAYAMA Ichiro EBARA Shingo
MIZUNO Kumi NAKAMURA Tadao
TAZAKI Jun
Director:
OKAMOTO Kihachi
Why are you following me?
I was going to ask you the same question.
Why do you keep walking in front of me?
If you try something, I'll kill you.
Same here...
but that scar of yours keeps bothering me.
Scar? I have no scar.
No need to hide it.
You do have at least one broken rib.
It must have broken when Saburoza's
sword guard hit your chest.
Is it painful?
- No.
You're bluffing.
You better stay around here until
winter's over and then calm down.
Calm down?
- Yes.
He's Takeda Shingen. He's not that easy.
He will find me no matter where I am...
You maybe right.
He will come looking for me
no matter where or what.
It must be hard to being chased.
What?
- Wait!
By the way... let me ask you something.
lf... if I am the person who is chasing you...
what will you do?
I will kill you.
You look serious.
But I don't want you to do
that. Do you know why?
I guess you don't.
Then I will tell you...
If I get killed now, Japan's
history will change...
You still don't get it, do you?
You are most confused.
You don't know the man's determination
to become the ruler of this country.
Let me ask you this...
If you succeed in getting away,
what are you going to be?
I will be the ruler of the country someday.
What's so funny?
Excuse me!
If you have to, can you
kill even your own family?
No, I don't think so...
If you try to be ruler of this dangerous
world, you have to have the guts to.
Otherwise, you better give up.
Maybe, it's too soon to be threatening you.
Or you should find a sponsor.
A sponsor?
- Yes.
You look around and find a
person you can take advantage of.
An example...
An example... who?
How about Kinoshita Tokichiro?
Kinoshita?
Tokichiro...
Don't you know him?
I don't know such a name.
Such a name?
If he is listening now, he will be so sad.
Oh, here they come...
What is that?
You don't know anything, do you?
They are Bashaku who
transports rice, salt and fish.
They are horse handlers.
If they are transporters, why
do they dress like samurai?
If they don't, how can they protect
themselves from bandits and ambushes?
I see...
It's a small world...
because there's always a place to
hide, at least one place or another.
How about we go there to join them to hide.
I think that's a good chance
to escape your pursuer.
Who are you?
I am the future ruler of
this country, just like you.
What are you doing here?
I am looking for that chance.
I want to use them to find that chance.
Are you trying to sneak in there?
No, but you do.
I am just watching from
here. Do a good job!
Tell me. How should I succeed?
Miss!
What's the matter, Matsu?
Some weird man is coming.
A weird man?
Help me! Help me!
Wait!
He's trying to kill me! Please help me!
Son of a bitch! Hey!
He's trying to kill me!
You poor farmer!
Help me!
Hey girl, let go of him!
I see, a hunter can't catch a bag if
a bag is hiding inside his nest...
You are a nuisance to the Bashaku!
What did you say?
I don't care if you are Bashaku,
but you better watch it!
What's all this about?
He's saying I stole his rice ball.
Yes, you stole it!
Is that true?
Yes, I was so hungry.
Both of you are chasing
each other for a rice ball.
You both must be so hungry.
How about if I let you join us?
Not me...
Let go of him! If you don't,
I will take him by force.
Be my guest! Bashaku of the Sakamoto,
the Ariyoshi will accept your challenge!
Interesting...
Come at me, Bashaku!
No, I quit! I'm so hungry, I can't fight...
So, are you going to join us then?
Yeah, seems like it.
Doko Harima will take your offer.
Harima...
you are a Hari (hedgehog). And you?
Let go of me! How long can you hang on?
My name is Kichi.
Let's go!
Wait!
Wait! Wait, I said!
Your loincloth is loose.
The game is over!
This is unfair!
A dead man shouldn't talk!
Next... it's you!
Roku, this is your arrow.
Target...
is that pillar.
How is the newcomer, Roku?
We can use him.
But he wasn't a samurai or farmer,
I don't know his background.
Boss, we better be cautious about him.
Oh yeah? But, everything is a mystery...
including you too...
What are you talking about?
I'm trying to say that it doesn't matter
who they were to become Bashaku...
so you better stop useless guessing.
We only want to find out if he can
handle a horse, or in good shape.
The Lady is back.
Miss Saghiri!
- Natsu!
Maybe you are an ex-samurai
but don't call me 'Miss.'
You are just Natsu of Bashaku now.
You better stop call me "Miss Saghiri".
Father, we brought the cargo safely.
Did anything happen
while you were travelling?
No, nothing happened.
Did you see any bandits?
Yes, we saw them, but
they didn't bother us.
But there is...
Yeah...
Who are they?
Yes, your daughter picked
them up while travelling.
Did she?
She picks up weird things.
You are farmers, aren't you?
Yes.
So, you're samurai?
- The two of you...
He's the leader of the Ariyoshi
party, Sir Ariyoshi Munesuke.
Can you carry a horse?
Carry a horse?
No, they're too heavy for me.
- Idiot!
The Master is asking you
if you can handle horses.
Oh, excuse me.
Of course I can, I was raised at a farm.
What is your name?
- Kichi...
Kichi Kichi Batta (grasshopper).
Grasshopper?
Yes, that's you.
Hari Hari... Harinezumi (hedgehog).
Hedgehog?
- Yes.
A grasshopper and a hedgehog.
You're now our members, so you
better go to the lake and clean up!
"Grasshopper" is a good name.
"Hedgehog" is a good name for you too.
That girl is really something.
We can use her.
Yes, we can. Is she innocent?
She's innocent all right.
She's a real woman.
Did you say woman?
Now I know the reason why
you hung on to her so long...
saying "Help me!"
If you're thinking about a woman...
you'll be a son-in-law of the Bashaku
instead of the ruler of this country.
You overreact.
What's the matter?
Who do you think they belong to?
They're mysterious.
Maybe, Takeda spies.
Do you want to go for it?
No, let's take off.
Get ready!
This is dangerous...
I don't know what will happen next.
This is not the time for to cool off.
This is the second time
today we're in danger.
Second time?
- Yes.
First that monkey...
He wants to rule and change
history, and trying to involve us.
If a ninja is trapped in someone's
tricks, the ninja will be no more.
This is my weak point.
I was almost trapped.
What is so funny?
Ochi Kittan, you have a very
good skill and technique...
but you don't know much. He's
Kinoshita Tokichiro himself.
What?
He's an Oda general who became
a hero in the war of Okehagi...
and his name is Kinoshita Tokichiro.
He can be a good sponsor for you.
He uses dirty tricks. That wild monkey!
By the way, Sir Kinoshita, it has
become a dangerous world.
Yes.
War after war and the
people don't believe in God.
God doesn't bless the framers...
and the greedy farmers just only
worry about how to get more land.
It is getting worse year after year.
What will our future be like?
But Sir Munesuke...
This hard administration will
change for the better soon.
I can hear peaceful music.
Music?
Yes. And the man who's playing
that music is Lord Oda Nobunaga.
He couldn't do it last year, but now
he's trying to take over the country.
Is that wild monkey trying
to take over the country?
I can't believe it.
Yes, maybe he can.
We should join him.
Join that wild monkey?
Yes, I am...
I heard all about this, and how powerful
they are. That's exactly what I heard.
Yes.
We just need one musket
to kill hundreds of people.
Lord Nobunaga needs this weapon to
take control over this trouble world.
Can you carry this, a total
of 300 to the land of Oda?
300?
Who's there?
Don't worry! They're just curious.
By the way Sir Munesuke...
I have secretly bought Takeda's 300 guns.
If you deliver safely and return with the
money, I will pay you 100 gold pieces.
You put me on the spot.
The Bashaku's job is to carry rice and salt.
I know that.
I was following you the last few days.
Munesuke, this is my plan.
No one will suspect Bashaku
is carrying muskets.
Even though if you are attacked, this is
a chance to show off Ariyoshi's power.
Our power is only to protect
from the bandits and ambushes.
My men are the same
as my own sons to me.
They are the Takeda and
we have to be determined!
She didn't have to hit so hard.
Oh, my head hurts.
You were right! Our
enemy is a real woman.
Our plan is delayed.
Don't be stupid!
I'm not a man who forgets his own
destiny because of a little woman.
Miss Saghiri...
Did you read the letter I gave you?
Miss, please let me know...
I can't take this any more.
He's not worthy to be a
samurai, acting like that.
We have to be careful.
Won't you go after them?
No, they will be back.
Batta!
I'm here!
Damn! They beat me again.
We lost! Roku I will challenge
you with this again.
I'm telling you, you better quit now.
Good morning.
You got up early.
Yes I did.
Miss Saghiri, I don't know what to do...
Your father doesn't talk to me at all.
He's so stubborn.
I am sorry.
I will ask someone else.
Anyway, would you please lend
me one of your Bashaku men?
Okay.
It's going to be hard for me to
carry the muskets all by myself.
It's easy for me to help you.
Matsu! Matsu!
Yes, Miss...
Come over here! You're impolite.
If I go over there, it's going
to be even more impolite.
You're weird...
Anyway, send someone over here!
Well... who should I pick?
If anyone wants to rent this, I will do so.
Rent us? Ha! Who would want that?
Batta... Are you there?
Batta! Are you there?
By the way, what happened with
work? Didn't you hear the drum?
Didn't you hear that? Hey,
why aren't you ready yet?
Matsu, you too. Why are you still naked?
Everybody go look for Batta!
Stable, charcoal room,
everywhere, go look around!
I'm sure, he was here...
Did he take off?
Batta is not that kind of man.
Batta... where are you?
There he is...!
Is it time to eat?
Damn you! He has some nerve...
Idiot, hurry up and come
down! Our guest is leaving...
Our guest?
Kinoshita Tokichiro.
He's going to be a good sponsor.
He's not my cup of tea.
If I was you, I would try...
Before I make him our sponsor, I want
to tie him up and make him scream.
Hey, Batta, hurry up!
Hey, hey, Batta....
Yeah...
Why don't you walk behind our master?
Anyway, it's not good manners
to walk in front of your master.
You're not my master yet.
I see...but anyway, you walk too fast.
I'm always walking like this.
Is that so?
I thought you walked fast 'cause
you're alwaying being chased.
No, this is just natural.
By the way, where is the chaser?
Is that your chaser?
Are you sure?
Don't be sure of yourself,
they might be chasing me.
Let's take a break!
That's a good idea.
What's going on?
Why did you hit me all of a sudden?
I had to get you out of the way.
Well, we better start going...
Hey, hey, Batta...
You're always walking in front of
me since the Bashaku house...
but do you know where we're going?
Yes, I can guess...
The port town of Sakai in Senshu...
and we're going to visit
Murakami Suigun, aren't we?
RYUSHINMARU
Everybody looks strong!
This is a big wide would...
but I think Murakami Suigun is
the one who should become ruler.
Therefore, I...
Tokichiro trust you and came
here to ask you a favor.
Didn't we?
- Yes.
What do you think? Please
listen to my request.
The muskets, 300 of them
to the port Asuda of Oda...
That's right!
Then, you will accept my request?
Well... I can't decide by myself.
Please, don't say that!
Our difference is only
land men and sea men...
but Murakami Suigun and the Oda clan...
we all relate to the family of Fujiwara.
If you understand, please
accept my request.
Please wait a moment!
Do you think we have a chance?
I don't know... Did Murakami Suigun
also come from the Fujiwara family?
I made it up. My tongue just
keeps going and I couldn't stop.
We're talking about 300
muskets, this is good news.
You think so?
Stupid...
If we can get those muskets,
we will be very powerful...
Truly, you are our princess!
This is Takihime.
She is beautiful!
A princess from the castle...
We accept and we will carry
the 300 muskets for you.
Are you sure?
I told you, I accept.
Excellent!
Kinoshita Tokichiro will never forget this.
Hyakuzo, he's our honorable guest,
serve him with our best Sake.
Sir Kinoshita, we can't find your partner.
Is that it?
Hey! Is that Murakami Suigun's
ship, the "Ryushinmaru"?
Hey, start up your ship!
Did you hear that?
Oh, you're Suzumeno
Saburoza, aren't you?
You're alive!
I can't die until I've sent Ochi Kittan to hell.
But Sir Saburoza, why are you here?
I'm waiting for a catch.
A catch?
Yes, I caught a big one already.
I caught two...
Two?
One is... The whereabouts of the muskets.
And the second one?
Ochi Kittan...
You chased him to the "Ryushinmaru".
Is he Tokichiro's partner?
Damn it!
Are you waiting for Kittan?
I was just getting some fresh air.
Miss...
I don't like dry air.
Let me hear your answer to my letter...
Wait!
Find out with that!
All right!
Harinezumi, good idea. I will teach you!
I'm not going to think of you as a woman.
Is that so?
I'll so no mercy.
I didn't expected any!
Well...call up all your courage and try!
Get ready!
The game's over!
If you continue, both will lose.
Her sword will hit his
shoulder and break it...
and his will hit her
kneecaps and break them.
You're talking nonsense.
Hey, dead men can't talk.
If this was a real fight, you
wouldn't have your head now.
I saw she got you first.
Batta, you should have let us
know as soon as you returned.
I was going to...
Come see me later!
Yes.
Is this going to be a punishment?
Who knows?
How was the trip?
They were persistent.
Did they come after you?
This...
This is Suzumeno Saburoza.
Is he still alive?
He's persistent.
How's Tokichiro?
He has skill of the tongue.
With his skill, he talked
Murakami into working for him.
Really? He talked with Murakami Suigun...
...that pirate...
Maybe they are toasting with Sake now...
Kinoshita Tokichiro has returned!
How's the situation here?
- As you told us...
Kinoshita Tokichiro is back now!
What's going on here?
I don't know...
We don't know... but he's
very interesting to me...
Sir Munesuke...
you came from the famous 5th
of the Fujiwara and ex-bandit...
because of this, I'm asking you?
Please listen to me and accept my request.
Miss... Do you want to see me?
You didn't come from a
farmer family, did you?
Yes, I am a farmer who was very poor
and didn't afford to eat decent food.
Then, how did you know
about the sword fight?
That... that was just my guess.
What?
Yes... I just couldn't stop my mouth going.
Yes, if you don't accept my request...
I don't know how to
face my lord Nobunaga.
Maybe I have to commit Harakiri.
Wait! Wait!
Then, will you accept?
Well...
No, you don't.
Well then...
Miss, stop joking!
I will find out if you are
a real farmer or not...
Stop that!
Someone help me! Help me!
Batta! Are you all right?
I like a woman who acts like a woman.
If you act like a tomboy,
you will not find a husband.
It's okay now...
This is a difference between
good skills and poor skills.
Aren't you going to say thank you.
Thank you?
You reminded me of the
blood of Takeda Shingen.
I didn't know Shingen was testing
me and I went over the fence.
I looked down the other side of the fence
and there was the mountain of swords.
That moment, I realized what
a cruel man Shingen is...
Fortunately, I was hanging on to a branch
of pine tree and managed to escape.
Harinezumi, how is it?
I'm not a great man like Shingen.
But, I was thinking that
might been possible...
Ah, you're getting better.
But you still can't read other's minds yet.
If you could do so, you're
going to be perfect.
Is everybody here?
Yes, almost...
Everybody is here now.
Okay...
Now, Sir Kinoshita Tokichiro has a speech.
He wants to ask everybody, if
we accept his request or not.
Well... Please listen everyone!
If I tell you, you can make one
gold coin a day, what do you say?
It's a big gold coin!
Sir... It's not possible
for such a job to exist.
Yes, it is...
It's going to take seven days
from Sakai port to Kiso river.
And seven pieces of gold...
Not a bad deal.
Also, we will give you a free ticket to
the land of Oda if you complete the job.
Do you want to do it?
I'll do it!
- Wait!
It's too good to be true.
What exactly are we to carry?
It doesn't matter what it is...
It might be a dangerous job...
but we will get seven pieces of gold...
or do you want to stay poor?
This kind of offer doesn't come too often.
Yes, I will do it!
This is a special bonus!
Me too! Me too!
You're going to take this offer, aren't you?
Yes... maybe...
I don't know.
Why don't you know?
300 muskets... Murakami
accepted, didn't he?
That's all part of my smart plan.
Smart plan?
- Yes.
Murakami and the Bashaku...
real muskets and fake muskets...
which do you think they will come after?
Which are real?
Well... which do you think?
What are you thinking about?
Heart... it's about heart!
When can we trust people...
Why we can't live honestly?
I thought you knew all about the
world, but you are still naive.
Even though we try to climb the mountain,
there's no straight mountain road.
I want to walk straight in this life.
Walk straight...
You can't survive in this troubled world.
They will kill even the
family if they have too...
And they lose their soul
depending on the situation.
It's too late to take a break.
If everything goes as planned,
it should take only seven days.
But if on the way, someone
interrupts us, I don't know...
I leave everything to you
now, and pray for your safety.
Father, we're ready to go.
Is everything set?
How is the number of people?
Well... we can't find Roku since last night.
Roku?
He's a useless man.
I will wait for your arrival at the river.
Go ahead, start!
I don't have to worry as
long you two are with them.
I'm depending on you.
Does he think we don't
know his sweet talk?
It doesn't cost him anything to sweet talk.
Just as I thought, he's a clever man.
Roku... it's okay now.
My Lord!
We succeeded!
Yes.
Now, we're going to be busy.
Yes, shall we start?
Yes, I'll let you take care of it.
Father, where are we staying tonight?
I would like to go to the river, but
we shouldn't rush the very first day.
Matsu! This is it for today.
This is a very easy first day.
Idiot! In the night, there are bandits
in the pass that attack people...
On behalf of Kinoshita Tokichiro,
Hachishika Goroku gaves this to you.
Ten in one bundle and
here is thirty bundles...
so all together it'll be 300 muskets...
I give to you.
Thank you, Goroku!
Maybe I don't have to tell you...
Be cautious! I know...
Yes.
Don't rush! Do it after the sunset!
Batta, don't neglect your job!
Something is going on...
It's too quiet.
Father!
They're here!
Who are you?
We know you're carrying
money to the Todaiji!
You better pay us some toll money!
Don't you know the
Bashaku Ariyoshi family?
Wow! Miss, you're brave!
You'll get hurt.
Wait! We'll pay the toll.
Father!
Shut up!
Here!
Don't make fools of us!
Do you think you can go
with this little money?
We'll pay whatever we want to pay.
We're not going to let you pass!
If you don't, we're going to do this...
Princess!
Who?
Suzumeno Saburoza of the Takeda
clan will take these 300 muskets.
What are you doing?
Princess!
They tricked us.
Get out of here!
Princess!
Tokichiro...
I won't let you get away with this!
Boss, this is a much easier
trip than we thought.
It's only the third day, it's
unbearable to have trouble now.
Do you think we'll have trouble soon?
We must be prepared.
Father, look! It's smoke...
Does it have something to do with us?
Yes, of course! It's a
signal from the bandits.
Maybe it's from the Takeda.
They're here! They're here!
Take positions!
Wait!
He's a captain of the Higo.
Sir Kinoshita, what's going on?
We're trying not to attract attention...
I know...
but the situation has changed.
Changed?
Yes, someone is trying to find out our plan.
Who?
Is it the man who made the smoke signals?
I don't know...
But, if someone made smoke
signals, good thing I came.
Wait! Where are you going?
I'm going to look for the person
who made the smoke signals.
No you don't! Don't leave
without my permission.
But...
You are making an excuse
to show off for Miss.
What did you say?
Don't pay attention, let's go!
That's right! That's right!
We're a stronger team now.
Look!
Those are 30 good men from the Oda clan.
I don't know...
What?
Are they really suitable?
Don't worry!
They aren't suitable for this,
nothing but dead trees.
We're leaving!
Let's go!
Look! That smoke again...
So, they're still watching us.
Father! There's a hindrance.
They're coming after us again.
Who are they?
They're not bandits. The way they
move, maybe they're Iga ninja.
That's right! It will be trouble if we
get involved. Let's ignore them.
Boss, we can't find Natsu.
You don't want to die, do you?
If you take care, you can
live at least 30 more years.
So, listen up! If you don't, I will kill you.
Now, I have to think serious.
Yes. There are Iga ninja on the right.
And bandits on the left.
Which is easier, bandits or ninja?
Ninja or bandits...
If we have a choice, the
bandits are much easier.
We're going through Suzuka.
Yes, we don't have a choice.
Okay, let's do that.
We're leaving! We're leaving!
Oh? He's coming back.
Forward!
Father, there's that smoke again...
They are persistent.
Ignore it!
- Forward!
We'll sleep here tonight.
We're going down the valley of Suzuka
tomorrow, you better get some rest.
It's a mess here.
Maybe, the people abandoned this
village because of the bandits.
This is common in war times, bad
guys attacking innocent people.
Matsu, how is the guard situation?
Two pairs at the north, one at
the west and one at the east.
You didn't forget to tie the horses, did you?
Yes, Miss.
It's a shame to keep her for the Bashaku.
Do you think so?
We should take her to the city of Miyako.
I don't agree with that.
Why is that?
I think Saghiri is happy where she is...
Didn't you call her "Saghiri" just now?
I see...
is that so?
What's the meaning?
Well, it's okay.
I have a good instinct
about this kind of things.
If you want to, I can bit for it.
We didn't know you had a talent like that.
Please keep singing!
Batta! Harinezumi! It's
time for to take the watch!
Yes!
Matsu, where's our position, west or east?
"We are sadly apart to
the west and the east."
It's my turn...
Okay, good.
Sir samurai...
Excuse me, Sir samurai?
Sir Samurai?
Are you talking to me?
Oh, it's a woman...
What are you doing here?
I'm a travelling Sake peddler.
I got lost on the way and
I don't know what to do...
A Sake peddler?
Woman, it's all right! Come
here and warm up by the fire.
Thank you.
I will do as you say...
Batta! Where are you?
He's really something!
Hyokuzo! Where are you?
Who are you?
Princess! Get ready!
Shut up!
Pick up the spear!
You're Munesuke's daughter, aren't you?
Who are you?
Murakami Suigun.
The pirate?
You can say that.
Hey, girl...
It's dangerous to walk
around at night alone.
Why don't you go home and sleep.
Shall I sing you a lullaby?
It's getting late, go to sleep.
Don't go against my word!
You are very weak... Its easy to fall...
Go to sleep... go to sleep...
That sword is too heavy for a girl...
and the arm holding it is
going down... going down...
Go to sleep... go to sleep...
You can't move!
Princess, what are we
going to do with her?
She is our hostage. Go and get everybody!
Are you a sexy fox or an old raccoon?
I am a sexy female fox...
Oh...it's you!
Takihime is here to ask you a favor.
A favor?
Okay, I'm very weak when
a woman asks a favor.
What do you want?
First, I'll serve you Sake.
I'm such a lucky man.
A beautiful woman came to see
me all the way to the mountain.
It's so bad.
But, I'll have another bottle here.
You're so well prepared.
This is great!
Good Sake becomes great when
a beautiful woman is pouring...
Won't you stay the night?
First... I want 300 muskets.
You want?
What ever happened to
the ones I gave you?
Tokichiro! Don't play games with me!
Calm down... My retainers will hear you.
Your retainers are all drunk and asleep.
What?
- That's right!
Poisoned sake...
I'll let you pour sake for
me too, the night is long.
Yes, the night is still long.
Let me play first and
then you can go to sleep.
You will miss me after tonight.
Batta!
Miss, everybody will start
worrying, hurry back!
Let me handle this! Hurry!
- No!
Miss, hurry and go back!
Saghari!
Kichi, what did you just call me?
Go back, Miss!
No!
Saghiri, you fool!
I'm going.
Kichi, you fool!
You are a good man.
Why did you rescue me?
I can't let a worthy man
die. It's one of my habits.
Don't you think, you're wasting
your time being a Bashaku?
Living as a Bashaku is
one of my bad habits.
Princess, some Sake?
Yes please.
Meanwhile, our people
will take the muskets.
What?
With no guards around, it's easy
to break in on a night like this.
I don't know about that...
I was stupid.
Why didn't I know about the fake muskets?
Because of that, the
Takeda wasted two days.
Maybe, Sir Kinoshita thought
Murakami has all useless men.
You better get out of here.
What about the Princess?
Why are you following me?
Why are you walking in front of me?
Why not walk beside me?
Interesting!
What's interesting?
A Bashaku and a pirate walking together.
Strange world, don't you think?
What's the matter?
It's my leg. I can't continue.
What shall I do?
I can't leave you all alone
Can you carry me on your back?
On my back?
Not a good idea, I have a sore back.
Okay, I'll carry you in my arms.
Here we go.
Ah, it's been a long time
since I smelled a woman.
It's such a sweet smell.
Just as I thought!
You better go back to your friends.
Son of a bitch!
This is going to be trouble.
Saghiri, did something happen to you?
No, nothing.
I slept so well.
I'm glad nothing happened last night.
Good God! The retainers of
Sir Kinoshita were attacked!
What?
They must have drank poisoned Sake...
and when they woke up,
no one could stand up.
Where is Sir Kinoshita?
He's not there, he left a note.
"The situation has changed, I'm leaving.
"Please take care of the
rest of the trip. Tokichiro."
All those samurai are not real samurai,
most are just men from the street.
I can't figure him out.
I'm beginning to understand...
Is that so?
Kichi, good morning! Father, lets get going!
You have a lot of energy this morning.
Did anything happen?
No, nothing happened.
Get up! We are leaving!
Kichi, where did Harinezumi go?
He's a grown man, he'll show up.
It's not easy to earn seven gold coins.
They will soon be ours.
I'm going to eat and drink all I want...
I want a woman, a woman who can cook.
Son of a bitch! I can't take this...
What's the matter?
What do you think?
Bandits from Suzuka.
We've been talking to Taro in Suzuka,
and bandits don't kill for no reason.
Kichi, what do you think?
They are theTakeda of Kosyu.
What?
I recognize the knife. We better get going.
Get going!
Here they come again! They're here!
Rikuhei! Rikuhei!
Riku! Riku!
Kichi!
I'm going down. If he's alive,
we can't leave him there.
But...
I won't do it if I think it's impossible.
All right! I'll go with him.
There's no reason to compete...
Did you find him yet?
Not yet!
The rope suddenly snapped, Kichi is gone!
Kichi!
There were very sharp edges.
His body is probably broken into pieces.
He was a good man.
Kichi...
Kichi...?
Miss, you'll have another hard
day tomorrow, get some rest.
Are you thinking about Kichi?
Miss, why won't you forget about
him. It was only a "grasshopper".
You...!
His death didn't bother you, but
a little cut on your hand does.
What are you saying? I try to
hide my emotions because...
Who is it?
I am Suzumeno Suburoza,
don't you remember?
You did a good job, well done.
You have killed four men already.
No, I've killed five.
The last one, why did you do it?
Do you know who he was!?
Kichi...
Yes, Ochi Kittan.
I wanted to kill him with my own hands.
I wanted to challenge him in public.
But, you still have work to do.
You have to leave enough men to carry
the cargo and then kill the rest of them.
By myself?
Don't worry, Taro of Suzuka will help you.
But, we'll get in trouble with
the Bashaku and the bandits...
Trouble?
It's easy, just give them some money.
Listen carefully.
First, we use the girl, Munesuke's daughter.
Saghiri?
What are you going to do with her?
You're in love with her, aren't you?
Then this job is perfect for you...
The bandits take Saghiri as their hostage.
You will inform Munesuke about it.
After everybody get excited, you'll go
after the bandits with half of their men...
and those men will get killed.
But you rescue Saghiri.
Isn't that great?
Go and do a good job!
See you at the Kiso river!
Miss! Miss!
Miss!
Matsu, what's going on?
The bandits have kidnapped Saghiri!
What!?
I'm going after them.
Please lend me some men!
I'm going too...
Let's go!
- No, that won't be necessary!
It's a ghost!
I'm not a ghost. I'm very much alive.
I had a bad experience though.
Kichi, you're alive!
Yes, I am.
How did you survive?
The Gods haven't abandon me yet.
Boss, don't send your
men, it's some kind of trap.
A trap?
Yes, because of the contact
with the Sazuka bandits.
The contract won't work
with the Bandits now.
Are you blinded?
You must be blinded too...
Can your men carry the cargo at night?
Yes, the moonlight will help guide us.
Then go ahead as fast and far as you can.
I'll rescue your daughter.
What? All by yourself?
I see. How many bandits are there?
50 or 60 bandits, so we'll need a lot of men.
If we take too many, her
life will be in danger.
Anyway, we'll attack them at the highway.
Boss, please let us go!
Okay, it's up to you.
We're going to wait for you down the road...
Thank you!
Thank you, I'm going too.
I'm hungry, do you have something to eat?
I don't like quite women.
Hey, stop that! Go and keep a look out!
They're coming soon...
The Bashaku...
The Bashaku, even children
can deal with them.
I'm not worried about them.
Taro, I can't wait...
I want her now!
Is your disease acting up again?
You'll have to wait!
I can't wait!
Shiro!
I want...
I want her!
- The Bashaku are here!
I would rather play with
you, than with the Bashaku.
Where are they?
This way...
Son of a bitch!
I want her! I want her!
Damn!
Oh, that's it.
Kichi! What's the matter?
Look at that!
Son of a bitch! Just wait,
I'll deal with you later.
Kichi, the smoke.
We better get going...
What's in your cargo?
In this? Oh, it's only firewood.
Where are you heading?
To Minu.
Minu?
What's in there?
There are sickles, hoes
and rakes. We're peddlers.
Check them out!
Sir, this is cruel! Cruel!
They're here!
All right!
Hold out! Hold out!
We'll soon take a break!
Boss!
Thanks for coming this far. We,
the Takeda will take it from here.
It must be a mistake.
This is Lord Oda's cargo.
It belongs to the Takeda now!
Bashaku, hand them over without trouble.
If you do that, we'll spare your lives.
The Bashaku will protect
this cargo with their lives.
For the sake of Kaen Daiko (The Flag of
Burning Drum), we will never yield to you!
Hurry up, use the musket boxes as shields!
Hurry up!
There are arrows everywhere!
Boss, we'll never reach the Kiso river now...
All right! We'll shoot them!
It's your daughter!
Boss!
Kittan... Good, you're still alive.
Father!
Are you all right? Don't give up the cargo!
Don't you ever let the Kaen Daiko ruin!
Saghiri, burn the cargo!
Before they can get their hands on it!
It's Harinezumi!
Long time no see!
Harima!
Somehow, I was worried about you.
I shouldn't have let you handle it alone.
What's that? By myself I don't
need to worry about anyone else...
That's right! That's what life is all about.
If you realized that, you finally
graduated from nursery.
You...!
They're coming back!
I'm wondering, how long he will last...
It's our sponsor.
He always shows up at the right time.
Good work!
How about those muskets, eh?
We need them in battle nowadays.
As long as we have them,
we can take over the world.
What about the muskets?
Ah that, Hashisuga Goroku
carried 300 of them, all by himself.
What?
He had a tough time on
the way, but he made it.
The Takeda was deceived
not once, but twice.
Sir Kinoshita...
What about our cargo?
Ah, Munesuke... it was only stone.
Stone?
- That's right.
Father!
- Tokichiro...
What about the people that got killed
because of the stones? Look at them!
"Kill the small insect and
let the large one live."
I see...
You're a man who can
kill even his own family.
Your way is the same as the Takeda,
only difference is, you use a brain...
Shingen doesn't.
You could say, it's your own fault,
but we can't help disliking you.
Do you understand, Monkey?
Yes, yes.
By the way, will you work for me?
I will guarantee that you will
rule a province someday.
No, thank you. I'm not that
desperate to become a ruler.
What are you going to do then?
I want to be a Bashaku.
I may be a small insect to you,
but I want to live like the weeds.
I will be strong even though stepped upon.
I realized this is the way
we're supposed to live.
Hey, we're going...
Kittan...
You've already matured.
He became a man while I was away.
You don't need me anymore.
Takihime, let's go.
Yes, but...
He'll be all right.
He will live like the weeds
together with Miss.
Isn't that right, Miss?
I will take Boss and Matsu with me.
They are both injured, so I'll take
them to the Dutch doctor in Sakai.
I'm not injured. I don't have a scratch.
You better take a look at your back.
Please take care of them.
I was going to depend on you.
You could have been a good sponsor.
Why did you change your mind?
Why not give it another thought?
I decided to go to sea.
Travel to Luzon, Siam, and Jakarta.
I'm getting cramped in this small land...
so we will be relaxing and wait till
the time you take over this country.
Take care!
How about you? Will you reconsider?
If I do, I'm afraid I might want to kill you.
So, your answer is no?
There's one more thing...
I don't know what you think of
me, but I'm also like a weed.
A man stepped upon many
times will became just like me.
In this world, there are many
different kinds of weed...
Ochi Kittan...!
I'm the loser...
Saburoza...!
It's Kaen Daiko (flag of the burning drum).
Let's build up the Bashaku again!
Subtitled and Mastered by Cannibal King
www.KuroTokagi.com